(Amy:)Come on, Sheldon. Why not?
(Sheldon:)For starters,
a bed-and-breakfast forces you
(Sheldon:)-to eat with strangers at your table.
-One step ahead of you.
(Amy:)Bernadette and Wolowitz
are going with us.
(Sheldon:)Very well. What are
the sleeping arrangements?
(Sheldon:)We've only been dating
for three years.
(Sheldon:)If we were to share a room,
people might talk.
(Amy:)I got you your own room.
(Sheldon:)What if my room has
a claw-toot bathtub?
(Amy:)It doesn't. I know it makes you feel
like you're bathing inside a monster.
(Sheldon:)Look, I appreciate the effort,
but I'm still unclear
(Sheldon:)how this trip is supposed
to be enjoyable for me.
(Amy:)We're going to have
Valentine's Day dinner
(Amy:)on a fully functioning vintage train.
(Sheldon:)Vintage? Be specific.
(Amy:)An Alcoa FA-4
diesel locomotive
(Amy:)leading a train
of meticulously restored
(Amy:)1915 Pullman first-class coaches.
(Sheldon:)Wow.
(Sheldon:)I'm feeling the urge to hug you.
(Sheldon:)And one... and two...
(Sheldon:)All right, Gollum, we're good.
I (THEME SONG) I